飞机马上降落在怀俄明州杰克逊城
We're beginning our initial descent to Jackson Hole, Wyoming.
感谢您搭乘美联航
Thank you for flying united.
估计我们很快就着陆了
Reckon we'll be landing soon.
菲尔 你保证落地前不变口音的
Phil, honey, you promised not till we got there.
我们今年要去度假牧场
This year we're going to a Dude Ranch.
全家一起
With the whole family.
"全是"家人呢
Mm-hmm the family.
带上迪兰吧 他自己出票钱
What if Dylan buys his own ticket?
我们保证分房睡
We'll sleeping in seperate cabins.
迪兰和我骑一匹马怎么样
What if Dylan and I share a horse?
我讨厌降落
Mm, I hate landing.
会挺过去的
We'll get through this.
干嘛呢这是
What are you doing?
我想把耳鸣"轰"走
I want my ears to pop.
涂些胭脂就"红"了
Try putting a little rouge on 'em.
我的笑点永远无人能懂
Nobody gets me.
景色多美啊 小牛仔女郎
Wow. Isn't this beautiful, little cowgirl?
你对她抢眼的打扮有意见 是不是
You hate her sparkly outfit, don't you.
不 我说过我没意见
No, I told you, it's fine,
我只是不喜欢你们穿父女装
I just didn't like you wearing a matching one.
我们还没有跟家人讲
So we haven't told the family yet,
但我们已经决定了要收养一个小男孩
but we've decided to adopt a baby boy.
这次要在美国收养
From America this time.
你也可以说我们在"支持国货"
You might say we're "Buying domestic."
私底下说 这种话只能私下说
In private. You might say that in private.
收养律师建议做一个相册
Our adoption attorney told us it would be a good idea
展示给未来儿子的妈妈看
to make a photo book to show prospective moms.
没错 但他认为小卡的版本太文艺装逼
Yes, but he thought that Cam's version was a little too "artsy,"
所以我们决定去农场拍些粗犷的照片
So, we decided to take a few rugged shots at the ranch to,
平衡一下
you know, balance it out.
我认为这相册不需要平衡
I don't think it needs balancing out.
不用吗
Really?
专业说法叫"产值"
It's called "Production value."
小马
Horse.
杰 快看 好骏啊
Look, Jay! So beautiful!
你仍处于耳鸣状态吗
Your ears haven't popped yet, huh?
我就像是"马语者"
I'm like the Horse Whisperer.
不过它不知怎么有点受惊了
But something is taking this one skittish.
放眼远山如黛
Look at the mountains.
真是巍峨秀丽
They're amazing.
我从来没有离家这么远过
I've never been this far from home before
现在又远了一步
now I've never been this far.
然后又远了一步
崖到跳时方恨少
Where's a cliff when you need one?
孩子们 看 实打实的牛仔
Look, kids! A real life cowboy.
来看 快来看
Oh. Come see. Come see.
他在干嘛
What's he doing?
老天啊
Oh, my.
我叫汉克
My name is Hank.
这里是失落河农场
Here at the Lost Creek Ranch,
在这里 你们可以骑马 抛绳和射击
you're gonna ride, you're gonna rope and you're gonna shoot.
夜晚可看到繁星满天
You gonna see a sky so full of stars,
都市的霓虹夜景也相形见绌
It'll put your city lights to shame.
远离喧嚣 洗尽浮华 或许你就会发现
And when it's all down, you maight just encounter
自己未曾发现过的真我
a piece of yourselves you never knew was there.
有什么问题吗
Are there any questions?
做水疗的话是向你预定 还是...
Uh, do we book spa treatments through you or...
我喜欢你 小子
I like you, kid.
我以后就叫你"好莱坞"
I'm gonna call you "Hollywood."
你没回答我的问题
That wasn't an answer.
这位仙人球是谁
And who's this Cactus Flower?
你说什么
What?
这是我妻子歌洛莉亚
That's my wife Gloria.
她以后就叫仙人球了 老前辈
Well, She's "Cactus Flower" now, old-timer.
这些个...绰号 都不能改吗
These, uh, these nicknames-- are they set in stone?
好了
Okey-dokey.
准备好了吗 枪手
You ready, gunslinger?
我听说这玩意儿不好使唤
I hear word of trouble in these parts.
上膛
Pull!
还行吧 杰
That oughta fix it, eh, Jay?
你有两下子
You got a piece of it.
我一直拼命训练
I been practicing like crazy.
所有的牛仔技能
All my cowboy skills--
射击 抛绳 吃煎饼
Shootin', ropin' pancake eatin'.
为何 因为有时候
Why? Because sometimes
我觉得杰不把我当男人
I feel like Jay doesn't respect me as a man.
每当说"菲尔是我女婿"的时候
It just when you say, "Phil is my son-in-law,"
像是说"菲儿 是我女婿"
It sound like you're saying, "Phyllis, come up, my son-in-law."
-别傻了 -那好 你女婿是谁
- That's ridiculous. - Okay, who's your son-in-law?
菲儿嘛
Phyllis.
我又不是说要个拥抱
I'm not asking for a hug.
我只想要一个肯定的眼神
I just want to get that look a newfound respect.
这样
Like...
或这样
Or...
或者这样
Or... mm.
不错
Yeah.
看好了
Check it out.
一腿二鸟
Two birds, one leg.
上膛
Pull it!
不错吧 老前辈
Not bad, eh, old-timer?
快看 三指火枪手
Uh, see, Slappy only had three fingers.
什么
What?
三指火枪手
He only had three fingers.
下一个谁来
Who's next?
我 我
Oh, me. Me.
这个好 这造型酷
Oh, this is good. This is good.
真男人
Tres macho.
不要笑 别笑 很好
No smile. Don't smile. Good.
准备好了吗
You ready?
等等 我是不是该喊"上膛"
Wait, do I say "pull"?
对不起 对不起
Sorry, sorry.
米奇尔 你还是去水疗馆找曼尼吧
Mitchell, why don't you go find Manny have the spa.
那可比这儿有趣多了
Wouldn't that be more fun?
好的
Yeah.
我终于明白 要养一个儿子
I realized that if I was gonna raise a boy,
我首先要爷们儿起来
I needed to butch up my life.
我希望我儿子从我身上学到的东西
You know, I wanted to be able to teach my son
就跟克莱尔从我爸那儿学到的那样
all the things that my dad taught Claire.
你好呀 好莱坞
Hey, Hollywood.
我不喜欢这称呼
I don't love that.
想不想看样东西
Wanna see something?
老天 你拿的是爆竹吗
Oh, my gosh. Is that a firecracker?
嘘
Shh!
我现在要好好想想要炸什么
Now I just need to find the perfect thing to blow up.
这玩意儿合法吗
Is that thing even legal?
在美国不合法 从德国偷渡过来的
Not here. It's from Germany.
如果二战的时候他们有这个
If they had this during the war,
现在咱们就要受德国面卷的祸害了
right now we'd all be knee-deep in strudel.
注意点
Watch it!
你在做什么 读书吗
What you doing, eh? You readin'?
欲读不能
Trying to.
我读书也不怎么好
I'm not so good at it either.
-可以预见 -开玩笑的
- I'm not surprised. - That was a joke.
我叫吉米·斯克利瓦诺
I'm Jimmy Scrivano.
想看我跳个炸弹开花吗
You want to see me do a cannonball?
我倒挺希望你被炸得开花 但...
I'd rather see you get hit by one, but...
妞 你真幽默
Ha. Good one, gorgeous.
杰 马和龙虾一样能吃吗
Jay! Is this like the lobster?!
晚餐能不能宰一头
Do I get to pick one for dinner?
这头看上去肉好嫩啊
Because this one looks very tender.
活力四射啊 老前辈
Look alive, old-timer.
你的一侧小腿肚都变形了
One of your calves is getting away.
我的马有点问题 她一直往左偏
Hey, something's wrong with my horse. She's veering left.
我叔叔中风那会也这样
When this happened, my uncle was at stroke.
"金凤花"可没什么问题
Oh there'nothing wrong with buttercup,
你得示示威让它知道谁才是主人
you just got to let her know who's the boss.
造型真漂亮 仙人掌
Beautiful form, cactus flower!
美极了
Beautiful!
看起来真像个西班牙马背女王
You look like a dadgum conquistadora!
她耳背 我可没有
She's deaf, but I can hear ya.
你为嘛要这个姿势
Why are you riding that way?
我害怕那边的牛会咬我
I'm afraid that cow over there might bite me.
它"当然"要冲过来咬你
Oh, yes, he's gonna come up and bite you
谁让你美腿配靓鞋 秀色可餐呢
because your leg looks so desirable with those--
你穿的是帆布鞋吗
Are those canvas?
菲尔 把后面那头轻轻赶到我这儿
Okay, Phil, ease that one back over towards me.
-收到 -轻轻赶过来
- Got it. - Ease him back this way.
嘿嘿 小菜一碟 是吧 杰
Hey! Piece of cake, huh, Jay?
-什么 -把那头赶到红太狼那儿
- Huh? - Ease that one over to Bossy.
哪头是红太狼
Which one's Bossy?
那是我给你老婆取的外号
That's my nickname for your wife.
真幽默
Hilarious.
老妈加油 哇哦
Go, mom! Whoo!
老妈加油 您"酷毙"啦
Yeah, mom! You rock!
我倒真想"毙"了你小子
Oh, I wish I had a rock.
对迪兰友善点儿又不会死
Hey. It wouldn't kill you to be nice to Dylan.
会死的
It might.
但亲爱的 我不明白为什么你总护着他
But, honey, I don't know why you always stick up for him.
海莉完全有资本挑个更好的
Haley can do so much better.
因为我明白深爱一个女儿
Because I know what it's like to fall for a girl
却不受岳父待见 是什么感觉
whose dad thinks I'm not good enough.
好吧 听你的
All right, you're right.
我尽量对他好点儿
I can make more of an effort.
这才是我心爱的女人
That's the woman I love.
两位是在这儿休息 打算云雨一番吗
we taking a little break over here? Laying some pipe?
对不起 我只是在和红太狼聊天
No. Sorry. I was just talking to Bossy.
-菲尔 -对不起
- Phil! - I'm sorry.
杰 看 我拦住这头了
Jay, look! I got this one!
我搞定它啦
I got this one!
我的马又开始往左偏了
She's veering left again.
等咱回去了 我倒要看看
When we get back, I'm gonna see
这货到底是不是斜眼
If she can track a pencil with her eyes.
好吧 莉莉 我就再推你一次
Okay, Lily, I'm going to push you one more time.
不要踢我哦
Now don't kick me, okay?
啊 莉莉
Aah! Oh! Lily!
我说了 别踢我 好吗
I said don't kick me. Okay?
你挨踢可不是她的错
You know it's your own fault that's happening.
干嘛不站在她后面推呢
Why don't you try standing behind her?
你是个白痴
You are an idiot.
是吗 被踢的可不是我啊
Oh, really? I ain't the one getting kicked.
你干嘛跟踪我
Why are you following me?
你干嘛非跟我吵 妞儿
Why are you fighting me here, gorgeous?
咱俩之间有戏
This works.
我真心 不喜欢
I really, really don't appreciate
你叫我妞儿
you calling me "Gorgeous."
我只想和家人享受美好时光
I just want to enjoy time with my family,
所以如果你不介意...
So if you don't mind--mm!
当然不介意 回见 阳光小美女
Not a problem. See you around, sunshine.
你亲了个男孩
You kissed a boy!
明明是他强吻我好不好 莉莉
No, the boy kissed me. Okay, Lily?
他吻我
The boy kissed me.
*人生第一次 把那马儿骑*
*I rode a horse for the first time today*
*马儿嘶嘶叫 吓我心儿跳*
*wasn't surprised when it went... neigh*
嘿 迪兰
Hey, Dylan.
你好呀 邓菲太太
Hey, Mrs. Dunphy.
我们谈谈行吗
I was wondering if we could have a little chat.
你想赶我走吧
Oh. You want me to go home.
不是 与你想的正相反
No, no. It's the--the opposite of that.
那就是"我想赶你走"
I want you to go home?
不 我想让你知道 有你同行我很开心
No, I, um, I want you to know how glad I am that you're here.
真的吗
Really?
有时候我觉得你不喜欢我
'Cause sometimes I just get this vibe you don't like me.
迪兰 不是的 真抱歉
Oh. Dylan, no. I'm sorry.
我喜欢你
I-I like you.
我好喜欢你 不过...
I-I like you a lot. I just...
情况比较复杂 因为海莉是我女儿
it's complicated because Haley's my daughter.
我靠 我靠 不是吧
Whoa. Whoa, whoa.
你虽然是个辣妈 但我不能违背伦常
You are totally a hot mom, but I can't do this.
我的天 乱了 不是这么回...不
Oh, my god. Okay, we--there's--no, no.
我只想说 要是怠慢你了 我道歉
I merely meant that I'm sorry if I made you feel unwelcome.
呼... 不然可就尴尬了
Whew! That would have been awkward.
超尴尬
So awkward.
但说句老实话 邓菲太太
You know, but for the record, Mrs. Dunphy...
什么
Yes?
如果海莉不是我女朋友
If Haley wasn't my girlfriend...
而且没有邓菲先生插足的话
and mr. Dunphy was out of the picture...
我愿与你同床共枕
I would be honored to share your bed
把卢克 艾丽克斯和海莉当做亲生孩子一样养大
And raise Luke, Alex, and Haley as my own.
好吧
Okay.
聊得很开心
Good talk.
*夕阳沉沉落山间*
*She'll be running down the mountain*
*夕阳沉沉落山间 明天悄悄再升起*
*She'll be running down the mountain when she comes*
歌两分钟前就该结束了
The song ended two minutes ago.
我跟你说 她都能演《艾薇塔》了
Well, I'll tell you what, she could play Evita.
是吗 你没发现连蟋蟀都走干净了
Really? You notice the crickets left?
还有人想喝水吗
Anyone want more water?
老爸 我要一瓶
Oh, Dad, I'll take one.
接住了
Heads up.
我的天啊
Oh! Oh, my gosh.
天太黑了 我没看见 谢了
Oh. It was--it was dark. I-I couldn't see it. Thank you.
你那个爆竹放了吗
So did you set off the firecracker yet?
如果我真放了 一定天下大乱
When I do, you won't have to ask.
首先 所有的电子产品都会失灵
First, all the electronics will go out,
接着热浪进袭
Then comes the heat flash.
之后 所有人都会生不如死
Afterwards, the living will envy the dead.
你如此残暴 上禁飞名单的竟然是我
And yet I'm the one on the no-fly list.
这样吧 下次由我来接
You know what? Maybe next time I'll just catch it,
然后把它递给你
and then hand it to you.
好吧 行 就那么做
Oh, okay. Yeah, let's do that.
你全部包办 我无所事事
You--you do everything, and I'll do nothing.
你有心事吗
Something on your mind?
众人面前 不方便谈这事
This isn't the right place to talk about it.
好吧
Okay.
我...我...
I-I'm s--
我在想到底该不该再要一个孩子
I'm not sure if we should have another baby.
什么 你说真的吗
What? Are you serious?
或许咱们有点操之过急
I think that we might be rushing into this.
操之过急 咱们已经努力
Rushing into-- we've been working--
各位 我是迪兰
Everybody, it's me, Dylan.
我只想谢谢大家能带我一起来旅行
I just wanted to thank you all for bringing me on this trip,
让我觉得如你们的家人一般
and making me feel like one of the family,
特别谢过红太狼
especially bossy.
我想趁此绝好时机
So I can't think of a better time
问问我心爱的女人
to ask something of the woman that I love.
好吧
Okay.
不 不
No, no.
海莉·格温多林·邓菲
Haley Gwendolyn Dunphy,
你愿意赐我殊荣
will you do me the honors
做我合法的妻...
of being my lawfully wedded--
停下 不行 不能求婚
No. No, no, no, no, no. No proposals.
现在不行 门都没有
Not now. Not gonna happen.
她还是个孩子 所以...
She's a child, so...
-妈 -你才是个高中生啊
- Mom! - You're still in high school!
可以等她毕业再结婚
I meant after she graduates.
现在不行 那时也不行
Not then. Not now.
永远都不行
Not ever.
说真的 你们俩要靠什么生活
Seriously, what are you two gonna live off of?
靠你那烂歌赚的版税
The--the--the royalties from the horsey song?
-把那玩意放回去 -你还有完没完
- Put it back in your pocket. - Would you stop it?
没完 绝对没完
No, I won't. I won't.
没事 没关系
No, it's okay.
我还是先回屋了
I guess I'll just turn in.
预先告诉你们一声 我小屋的风扇不好
Just so you know, there's a fan in my cabin
声音如泣似诉
that sounds like someone crying.
迪兰 等等 我恨你
Dylan, wait! I hate you!
算了吧 海莉 回这儿来
Oh, come on. Haley, get back here!
菲尔 能说句话吗
Phil, anything?
你说得就够多了 克莱尔
I think you said it all, Claire.
你想让我把她捆起来吗
You want me to rope her?
我可以的
I can, you know.
听不听由你们
For what it's worth,
当年我第二个老婆就是高中生
my second wife was in high school.
甜心 这儿 看着
Sweetie, here. Here we go.
-一 二 三 -一 二 三
- One, two, three. - One, two, three.
-没啦 -它不见啦 它在那儿呢
- Gone. - It's gone! It's over there!
它不在那儿
It's not back there.
-我们是数到三的 -对
- We counted to three. - Yes.
你去哪儿了
Where have you been?
我昨晚在门房睡沙发
I-I slept on the couch in the lodge.
我知道你昨晚不想跟我大吵
I know you didn't want to have a big fight last night.
现在我准备好了
Well, I'm ready now.
小卡 对不起
Cam, I'm sorry.
要是我没法做那些父子活动怎么办
Look, what if I can't do the father-son stuff?
打猎啊 运动啊
The hunting, the--the sports,
看《活宝三人组》啊
the Three Stooges?
你知道现实生活是什么
You know what happens in real life
要是有人脑袋让梯子砸了
when someone gets hit in the head with a ladder,
他们会去医院做核磁共振
they go to the hospital and they get an M.R.I.
那片子里可没这么演
Never see that scene.
我觉得你想得太多了
I think you're overthinking this.
我爱运动 我爱看《活宝三人组》
You know, I love sports, I love the stooges.
我们能搞定的
We've got this covered.
不 不是的 你能搞定
No. No, you--you got it covered,
但是我只能坐冷板凳
but I'm just stuck on the sidelines,
假装懂得那些规则 而且...
pretending to understand the rules, and...
我爸一贯狂野粗暴
You know, my dad was a rough-and-tumble guy.
我...我向来和他难以兴趣相投
And I just-- I could never relate to him.
我不知道 我觉得我无法承受
And I don't know. I just don't think I could handle
和父亲 儿子的关系都很失败
disappointing... two generations.
我觉得你比你自己想象的
I think you're more masculine
要爷们儿得多
Than you give yourself credit for.
谁把鸟巢建在走廊旁边的
Who puts a birdhouse next to a porch?
克莱尔 我知道你害怕
Claire, I know that you're worried
迪兰会玩弄海莉的感情
that Dylan is gonna break Haley's heart,
但我从他眼中读出了
but I see in his eyes
白头到老的执着
that he's gonna stick with her forever.
无论怎样 他都会跟她在一起
No matter what, he's always going to be with her.
等到你临终前
On your deathbed--
好了 行了 我受不了了
Okay. All right. I can't take this anymore.
我得去找她
I'm gonna go find her.
不行 逼得太紧只会适得其反
No. You push too hard, you chase her right into his arms.
到时候那个蠢蛋就真成你女婿了
You'll end up with a boob for a son-in-law.
相信我 你绝对不想变成那样
Believe me, you don't want that.
你这话是什么意思
What's that supposed to mean?
-怎么了 -你们有人看见迪兰了吗
- What? - Hey, have you guys seen Dylan?
没 没有 怎么了
No. No. Why?
我不想理你
I'm not talking to you.
他昨晚说过要出去走走
He said he was going out for a walk last night,
此后他就一直不见踪影
and no one's seen him since.
亲爱的 我敢保证他没事
Sweetheart, I'm sure he's fine.
可能他昨晚直接回家了
Maybe after last night, he just went home.
不太可能 他行李还在这呢
Doubt it. He left his luggage.
我们得想想办法
We have to do something.
一天不吃上五顿饭 他就会"飘然若仙"
If he doesn't eat five times a day, he gets spacey.
真想看看那是什么样子
What would that even look like?
我们会找到他的 汉克
We'll find him. Hank?
我们这儿出了点状况
We got a situation here!
什么状况
What seems to be the trouble?
我们得谈谈
We need to talk.
谈什么
What?
你偷走了我的初吻
You stole my first kiss.
有没有搞错
What are you talkin' about?
我早幻想过了
I had it all planned out.
我的初吻经历要很特别
It was supposed to be special,
他必须成绩倍儿棒 前途无量
someone with a high GPA And a bright future,
而不是"马里奥兄弟"
not a Mario Brother.
好吧 听着 我压根不稀罕你的吻
Fine. You know what? I don't even want your kiss.
拿去 还给你
Here, you can have it back.
好了 咱俩扯平了
There. Now we're even.
你自个儿留着吧 我不想要了
Well, keep it. I don't -- I don't want it anymore.
我在干什么啊
What am I doing?
好了 大伙儿听着
Okay, people.
看来我们之中有人走失了
Looks like we have a walker.
此刻他面对的是险恶的地形
Right now he is facing treacherous terrain,
以及暗洞 山狮和饿熊
sudden drops, mountain lions,
对了 还有狼獾呢
hungry bears, oh, and wolverines.
前提是他还没被冻死
That is, if the hypothermia didn't already get him.
为什么又故地重游了
Why did we come here again?
我们最好兵分三路
So our best bet is to split up.
你俩负责搜索北面步道
You two are gonna take the North hiking trail.
-我能和我爸一队吗 -不行
- Can I go with my dad instead? - Negative.
水牛菲尔和老前辈
I need buffalo phil and old-timer
得沿着斯内克河前进
to check the Snake River.
水牛菲尔
Buffalo Phil --
最后的才是最好的绰号啊
worth the wait.
我和仙人球负责天命山脊
Me and cactus flower will ride on up to Destiny Ridge.
应该让我陪她才对吧
Maybe I should ride up there with her.
没门儿 那条路线只适合高阶骑手
Negatory. That trail is for advanced riders only.
我可不想再出人命
We don't need another dead body.
"再出人命"
"Another"?
上马 出发
Let's go! Move 'em out.
菲尔 帮我挂上马鞍 行吗
Phil, help me saddle my horse, will ya?
瞧瞧岳父大人在向谁求助
Well, look who's suddenly needed by his father-in-law.
菲儿啊
Phyllis.
菲尔
Phil --
是也
is.
米奇舅舅 你在做什么
Hey, uncle Mitch. Whatcha doing?
你好
Oh, hey.
想些心事罢了
Just -- just thinkin'.
听着 我一直想告诉你
You know, I've been meaning to tell you,
你是个超有趣的舅舅
you're a super fun uncle.
这可是小男生的肺腑之言
And I'm saying this as a boy.
是卡梅隆舅夫派你来的吧
Uncle Cameron sent you over here, didn't he?
什么 别搞笑了
What? That's hilarious.
我就爱你跟我这样开玩笑
No, I love how you and me can joke like this.
卢克 听着 我不知道小卡向你透露了多少
Okay, Luke, look, i don't know how much Cam told you,
但我觉得 这种问题
but I don't think this is a problem
你帮不了的 这事...
that you can help me with. It's...
好吧 我承认 是我自己遇到了问题
Okay, good. I've got my own problem.
什么 怎么了
What? What's that?
你能替我保密吗
Can you keep a secret?
说吧 我将一个大秘密守了22年[同志身份]
I kept a pretty big one for 22 years, so...
我有个没用过的爆竹
I've got this new firecracker,
不知道该拿它来炸什么
and I can't decide what to blow up.
卢克 这玩意很危险
Oh, Luke, that's dangerous.
我知道 玩的就是心跳嘛
I know. That's what's fun about it.
我真搞不懂男孩子们
I don't get boys.
搞破坏有什么好的
What is so great about destroying things?
碎片四溅的多过瘾啊
It turns stuff into flying chunks of stuff.
好吧 不 交给我 快点
Okay, no. No, g-give it to me. Come on.
好吧
fine.
算我看错你了 你没那么有趣
I take it back. You're not that fun.
好吧 不如这样
All right, hey, look, um,
我们一起点了它 好吗
we'll do it together, all right?
你刚做了你这辈子最正确的决定
You just made the best decision of your life.
该死
Damn it!
金凤花 这马出了什么毛病
Buttercup! What the hell's wrong with this horse?
杰
Jay.
我想和你谈谈
I want to talk to you about
你早餐时说的关于女婿的言论
that son-in-law crack you made at breakfast.
-我没什么特别的意思 -我觉得你有
- Oh, I didn't mean anything by that. - I think you did.
我知道我不是你最中意的女婿人选
I get that I wasn't your first choice to marry Claire,
但结婚十八年来 我没有哪一天
but it's been 18 years, and there hasn't been a day
对克莱尔不是一心一意
when I wasn't a loyal husband to your daughter
对你的孙子孙女不是疼爱有加
and a great dad to your grandkids.
要是你还不满意 那就是你的问题
So if we've still got a problem, now it's your problem.
菲尔 等会儿
Phil, wait up.
我问你一个问题 男人之间的对话
Let me ask you something, man to man.
问吧
Okay.
你有没有注意到...
You notice anything funny about the --
汉克那家伙和...
Hank character and, uh...
歌洛莉亚吗
Gloria?
当然了 他在勾引她 怎么了
Yeah, he's hitting on her. Why?
我就知道
I knew it.
你要去哪儿
Where are you going?
天命山脊
Destiny ridge.
金凤花 驾
Buttercup, ha!
金凤花 驾驾
Buttercup, hiya!
有没有搞错
Seriously?
没问题 鸟屋是空的
Okay. Okay, it's clear.
炸了它 就能看到真实版愤怒的小鸟了
After this, we're gonna have some angry birds.
没错
Yeah.
我们就该喊"拜拜小鸟"
It's gonna be "Bye Bye Birdie."
那是六十年代的一台大型音乐剧
It's a big musical from the '60s.
算了 还是叫愤怒的小鸟吧
No. Forget it. What you said.
可以了
Okay.
好 撤
Okay, go.
就这样吗
That's it?
很遗憾 老弟
I'm sorry, buddy.
亏我大老远买过来...
I brought that thing all the way from...
小卡 我终于做了件男人的事 我把鸟窝炸了
Cam, I did a boy thing! I blew up the birdhouse!
你真该看看 酷毙了
You should have seen it. It was so awesome.
太棒了
That's great!
是的 我觉得我能行
Yeah. I think I can do this.
我是说 或许还要一步步一件件来
I mean, maybe not everything and maybe not right away,
-暂时无法忍受《活宝三人组》 -那就不看
- and not the Three Stooges... - No.
我确定了 我想要一个儿子
I do. I want a son.
对不起 之前有点恐慌
I'm sorry I panicked.
那好极了
Oh, that's great.
我们继续拍照攒相册吧
Now maybe we can go back to taking pictures for the book.
好啊 拍张我炸飞鸟窝的照片
Yes! Pictures of me blowing up stuff!
好吧 我觉得咱矫枉过正了
Okay, I see we've overcorrected.
我知道你认定我是个毒妈
I know you think I'm the mean mom
棒打鸳鸯 不准你们结婚
who wouldn't let you marry your boyfriend,
但是总有一天你会明白
but someday you're gonna realize,
我这么做是为你好
I did what had to be done.
不 别狡辩 我从来就没有打算跟迪兰结婚
No, you didn't. I was never gonna marry Dylan.
我拒绝了他
I told him no.
真的吗 谢天谢地
Oh, you did? Thank god.
他是向我求婚 要由我来拒绝
But it was my proposal to turn down.
你一直让我像个大人
You know, you keep telling me to act like an adult,
但你从来不给我这个机会
but then you don't even give me a chance.
你真说到点子上了
Oh. You sort of got me there.
但是 亲爱的 我不指望你知父母心
But, sweetheart, I don't expect you to understand this.
在你这个年纪的时候 我也不懂
I certainly didn't when I was your age.
在我心目中 你只是个孩子 永远都是
I look at you as my baby, and I always will.
当妈的都这样
It's just what moms do.
我不是小孩子了
I'm not a baby anymore!
明白吗 我再也见不到迪兰了
Okay? And I am never gonna see Dylan again!
迪兰
Dylan!
什么事
What?!
你在哪
Where are you?!
怀俄明州
Wyoming!
你没事
You're okay!
我度过了有生以来最疯狂的夜晚
I had the craziest night.
你拒绝我后 我觉得很迷茫 很害怕
When you rejected me, I felt lost and scared.
后来我就出去走走
And then I went out on a walk,
走着走着我真迷路了 才真害怕了
and I felt a whole different kind of lost and scared.
后来我在马厩睡着了
And then I fell asleep in the stable.
醒来时 我碰见了一位叫杰克的女人
And when I woke up, I met this woman named Jake
她壮得像个爷们似的
who's strong like a man.
我们谈了很久 他或者她 雇佣了我
Then we had this long talk, and he/she hired me.
什么叫她雇佣你了
Uh, what do you mean, she hired you?
我现在在这工作了
I work here now.
你要留下来吗
So you're staying?
-是啊 -那我们怎么办
- Yeah. - What about us?
我们走不到一起的 你我门不当户不对
It could never work. We're from two different worlds.
你是高中生
You're a high school student,
而我是农场工人
and I'm a ranch hand.
你没事 你没事我很开心 真的
I'm just--I'm so glad you're okay. I really am.
谢谢 但我们是不能和客人太亲密的
Thanks. But we're not supposed to fraternize with the guests.
好吧
Okay.
迪兰
Dylan!
你的声音好响亮 像草地鹨似的
You got a voice like a meadowlark, don't ya?
迪兰
Dylan!
我真为那孩子担心
Yeah, I sure am worried about that kid.
迪兰
Dylan!
他又不在我屁股底下
He ain't down there.
拜托 你来这是为了体验牛仔生活
Oh, come on now. You come up here for the cowboy experience.
你面前这位就是牛仔
You're looking at him.
我看起来像是水性杨花的女人吗
Do I look like the kind of woman that would cheat on her husband?
是的
Yes.
真的吗
Really?
你小子 最好离我女人远点
Hey! I think you better move away from that woman.
我们的女人要拒绝 也只有我们能霸王硬上弓
Only we touch our women when they don't want us to.
别紧张 朋友
Easy. Easy there, friend.
我没有勾引这个女人
I wasn't hitting on this filly.
这是旅游项目的一部分
This is all part of the package.
如果我不扮恶棍
If I didn't play the bad guy,
他也就没机会骑马赶过来 英雄救美了
he wouldn't get to ride up and be the big hero.
不需要你来衬托他的英雄形象
He doesn't need you to make him a hero.
他天天都是英雄
He's a hero every day.
你识趣一点吧 骑上马
Why don't you do us all a favor? Get back on your horse,
回到旅馆 告诉他们
ride down to the lodge and tell 'em--
你能让他别动吗
Can you keep him still?
-我在说话呢 -我尽力了
- I'm trying to make a point. - I am.
好的 我就走
Okay. Okay, I'm gone.
女士
Ma'am.
等等
Wait. Wait.
你给我听好了
There's something I wanna say to you.
你们的客户点评卡上
I will only be checking "somewhat satisfied"
-我只填基本满意 -老天啊
- on our comment card. - Jeez.
他对孩子们很好呀
I mean, he was great with the kids.
我查过了
I looked it up.
我们房子之间的距离是2443英里
The distance between our houses is 2,443 miles.
但是有些地图上
Yeah, but, you know, on some maps,
只有这么短
it's like--pfft! this big.
天呐 你真笨
God, you're stupid.
总而言之 这个假期棒极了
All in all, it was a great vacation.
或许我们失去了一个人
We may have lost a man...
但在茫茫山野 苍苍天穹之中
But out there on the range, under that great big sky,
我们发现了 自己未曾发现过的真我
we found a part of ourselves we never knew was there,
真被那个色鬼牛仔说中了
just like the horny cowboy said we would.
别这样
No.
好吧
Fine.